[
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "(x+2) (x-3)",
    "choice2": "(x+4) (x-1)",
    "choice3": "(x+2) (x-2)",
    "choice4": "(x+3) (x+1)",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "23",
    "choice2": "53",
    "choice3": "31",
    "choice4": "57",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "10",
    "choice2": "20",
    "choice3": "8",
    "choice4": "5",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "8",
    "choice2": "10",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "4",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "-5",
    "choice2": "-3/4",
    "choice3": "-3/2",
    "choice4": "2",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "21ab",
    "choice2": "-7b +14a",
    "choice3": "-7b -6a",
    "choice4": "14a -7b",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "10",
    "choice2": "7",
    "choice3": "20",
    "choice4": "4",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "20 -10a +10ab",
    "choice2": "-10a +10ab +20b",
    "choice3": "+10ab -10a +20b",
    "choice4": "+20ab +20b",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "10",
    "choice2": "4",
    "choice3": "8",
    "choice4": "12",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choice1": "<",
    "choice2": "+",
    "choice3": ">",
    "choice4": "=",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
